"The Luckiest Kid in the World."
They say angels have wings and fly.
But my angel is always by my side
and never leaves me.
She makes sure I'm always full
and delighted.
She is the reason
behind my every giggle and smile.
My mother never forgets to hug me tightly.
In her arms, I find peace and safety.
And because my mother loves me so much,
there's nothing more
I could ask for in life.
I am the luckiest kid in the world.
-Chairmom! Chairmom!
-Ms. D! Ms. D! Oh--
-Be careful.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Ms. D?
-Yes?
Is it true
that you're making an announcement
at the anniversary celebration
of La Familia?
Any spoilers?
Where did you hear that?
I'm sorry, no spoilers.
Ms. D? Today is the anniversary
of the factory fire, right?
What can you say about it?
Will today be a celebration
instead of a commemoration of the tragedy?
As the matron of La Familia,
I make sure
that we always prioritize the company,
our employees' welfare,
our work ethic,
and most especially, our safety standards.
That's how we commemorate the fire.
We honor it not by forgetting,
but by rebuilding and moving forward.
I'll see you later, okay?
Thank you so much.
-Thank you, Ms. D!
-No more questions.
A beautiful morning, Ms. D!
As beautiful as the outfit
you're wearing today.
You look very powerful.
-But also very motherly.
-Good morning, Ms. D.
Yes. You are radiant.
Oh, enough of the pleasantries.
Is everything ready?
O-Of course, Ms. D.
It's all set.
I can assure you that
everything will go smoothly.
I made sure that
there won't be any problems.
You have nothing to worry about.
Well, there better be none.
Yes, yes.
-Mm.
-Enzo.
Good morning, Ms. D.
Everyone is waiting.
Okay.
Come here!
Stop her!
-My baby!
-Get it!
No! My baby!
Come on!
Cut! Cut! Cut!
What the hell? You showed the doll!
You're not supposed to show
that the baby's a doll!
Unbelievable!
Excuse me. How'd I do?
I really gave it my all.
Huh? Girl, we weren't rolling.
Remember, the director wanted to show
Bianca and Daniela
a run-through of the scene.
Snap out of it.
This isn't your first time!
Director? Hold it.
We're good, Sandy.
Daniela, did you see what the woman did?
-Just do exactly what she did.
-Yes, Director.
Bianca, you're doing what Patricia did.
Sorry… Sorry, Director.
I was texting my manager,
I didn't see it.
Sandy, one more time.
From the top.
Tell the stand-ins
to throw in more punches.
And really knock her to the ground.
From the top.
More punches, more violence.
Okay? From the top.
First position, let's go!
From the top, ma'am?
Did I stutter? Are you deaf?
-No, ma'am.
-Good. Let's go,
let's go! Reset!
-Sis, you good?
-Reset! First position!
Let's go, let's go!
-I'm good.
-From the top!
In five,
four, three…
Good afternoon, everyone.
And welcome to this
very special celebration
for La Familia Corporation.
Today marks another
exciting milestone for La Familia.
As we celebrate our 50th anniversary,
we take our biggest step forward yet.
And now, please welcome
the woman leading La Familia
into the future.
The Nation's Chairmom,
Diana Aragon!
Good afternoon, everyone.
Thank you for coming.
For generations,
Cala Soda has been a part
of every Filipino family.
I've always said that
we're the silent member
of every Filipino family.
We're there
at every occasion and milestone.
Because that is what La Familia
has always been about.
As we celebrate our anniversary
with all of you all over the country,
we've continued our company tradition
of feeding communities across the country.
But today, we take our biggest step yet.
We are very proud to announce to you
the partnership between La Familia
and Burger City International.
They will now carry Cala Soda
and the entire line
of La Familia beverages
in their world-famous
fast-food chain branches
as La Familia officially expands
across all of the Asia-Pacific region.
But that's not
our only surprise today.
I proudly present to you
a new logo
that celebrates the partnership
between La Familia and Burger City.
Oh, my…
Hey, you guys thirsty?
-Hey, bestie.
-I have water and coffee.
Have you sold a lot?
One of them didn't pay.
Are you all thirsty?
Coffee? Water? Anything?
Get your drinks!
Director!
Uh… Are you hungry?
I have some fried buns!
It's my specialty.
-Look.
-How much?
Oh, it's on the house.
-Did you put poison in it?
-Of course not!
Mm. It's good.
Thanks.
Uh… I hope you can
consider me for your next show.
-Mm-hmm.
-But maybe not as a stand-in.
You could throw in some lines for me.
You saw me act earlier, didn't you?
What a suck-up.
She's so annoying.
Someone ought to teach her a lesson.
-What do you mean?
-Thank you, sir.
Director!
-Time to pack up.
-Okay. Let's go then.
It's a wrap, talents!
Time to move to the next location.
-All right.
-Patricia, where's the scarf?
Oh, here.
Why are you still in costume?
Get changed. We need that costume.
Okay, okay.
-Hand it over afterward.
-Yes.
-Go ahead. I'll follow.
-You sure?
-Yes. See you there.
-Okay.
Patricia, did they tell you
we're changing locations?
-No. Where's the new location?
-Here.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
You can drop me off here.
Thanks.
INDUSTRIA STREET
Hello, ma'am?
Where are you?
We're about to start rolling!
Yes. I'm already here at Industria Street.
What are you doing there?
I was told the location
was changed to here.
The location has not been changed!
Oh, my god!
I'll be there. I can still make it, ma'am.
Screw this!
Your miscommunication isn't my fault!
I can still make it, ma'am! I'm nearby!
Hello? Ma'am? Hello?
What happened?
I'm so sorry, Ms. D.
It was Mabel's responsibility.
She was in charge
of the technical rehearsal.
She didn't do her job properly.
Is that so?
Yes, Ms. D.
You know what happens to people
who don't live up
to my expectations, don't you?
Of course. Right away.
-Mabel.
-Ma'am?
-I'm so sorry. You're fired.
-Huh?
No. Ma'am, please.
There's nothing I can do. Ms. D said so.
-So please pack your things.
-Ma'am, please.
Sorry, you're fired. Bye! Bye!
I want you to revoke access
for employee #42568.
Escort her out of the building
immediately.
-Enzo.
-Uh…
Don't.
She's fired.
Ms. D?
You know why I fired her, don't you?
Yes, Ms. D.
Because this deal is very, very important.
Not just that.
What I hate most is a leader
who cannot take accountability.
Your people's failure is your own failure.
And worse, she shifted the blame
for something she was responsible for.
Ms. D? Ms. D?
How long have you been
working for me, Enzo?
Um, it's been seven years.
Since I graduated.
Congratulations.
You're my new Chief of Staff.
Let me fix this, Ms. D!
-Let's go.
-No!
No, Ms. D! Don't fire me!
One more chance, Ms. D! Ms. D!
Sir, don't do this. Don't do this! Please!
-Bestie.
-Oh, bestie.
What happened? Where were you?
That witch Riza sent me
to the wrong location.
Huh? She was the one who replaced you.
Because you weren't here.
Where is she? Where is that witch?
Riza! Hey, Riza!
Hey! Come out here.
Come on! Why'd you do that?
How could you--
Ms. Daniela!
Ms. Bianca! Come to set.
-Ms. Daniela! Ms. Bianca!
-Come out, Riza.
-Come on. Let's go.
-Bestie, I've got to go.
-I'm in that scene. Okay.
-All right, go ahead.
Actors are in, Riza. Come out there.
Talk to me!
You don't want to come out?
Five, four, three, two…
-Action!
-Can I help you?
Excuse me?
How much for the barbecue?
Ten--
Sandy, her reaction.
-Patricia, your line!
-Miss?
-What is going on? Patricia!
-What's the holdup?
We're running out of time!
Come on!
Can we do it or not?
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Yes. I can do this.
-S-Sorry.
-Hey!
-What now?
-I'm supposed to be in the scene.
-Can you do it?
-Sorry, I'm late.
You're too late.
From the top.
-Okay, let's go.
-Yes, one more.
-You!
-Hey.
You locked me in the porta potty!
-What's going on?
-The nerve of this girl!
You're not fighting fair!
You sent me to the wrong place!
-You want a fair fight?
-Oh!
Come here!
Stop it! Both of you!
Out of my set! Jeez!
Huh? Why am I getting kicked out?
I'm just doing my job. You know me.
I never cause trouble.
-Director, she started it.
-She provoked me.
-No, she did it.
-Then she's out!
For Pete's sake…
Are you okay, Miggy?
-Oh, my goodness.
-Again! Again!
-Are you okay? Okay.
-Yes.
-From the top!
-I'm good.
Your line, Patricia.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Okay. Ready?
-Ready. Roll!
-Rolling!
Five, four, three, two…
-Action.
-Action!
Excuse me, miss.
How much for the barbecue?
Ten pesos!
She told me to fire Mabel. Fire her!
And then when I came back--
Ms. D! Ms. D!
-Ms. D! Ms. D!
-Ms. Cynthia. Ms. Cynthia.
Please, hear me out! Ms. D, please!
Let go of me, Enzo!
-Enough.
-Ms. D!
It wasn't my fault!
The prop malfunctioned!
It was out of my control!
Well, that is what happens
when people like you come unprepared.
That's it? One mistake?
I gave 15 years of my life
working for you!
Ms. D, this is ridiculous!
That one mistake
happened on the most important day,
one that would shape La Familia's history
on the global stage.
So don't act like you're some victim,
like I did this to you.
You did this to yourself.
This isn't the first time you screwed up.
You've been warned several times.
And that is how accountability works.
That's not accountability!
It's cruelty!
No wonder no one loves you!
No wonder your family abandoned you!
This is why you're alone!
"Chairmom"? It's all for show!
Karma will come back for you!
Karma is no match for Diana Aragon.
You're the devil!
You're the devil! You ruined my life!
You ruined my life!
You won't get away with this!
You will pay for this!
La Familia!
What's… What's that smell?
Did someone cook dried fish?
We cooked it in the back kitchen, Ms. D.
Hours ago.
How many times have I said
I don't want to smell dried fish here.
Diana, you look tired.
Come. Chef has cooked dinner.
Nanny, have I not made myself clear?
I don't want to smell dried fish here.
Just ignore it. I'll remind them.
It's the anniversary
of your father's death soon.
I've had his mausoleum cleaned,
as you said.
Thank you, Nanny.
I'm sure your father is very proud of you.
La Familia has taken off since…
I'll have your dinner served.
There.
-Jeez, Jena.
-Okay, that's good.
-Oh! Hey, sis!
-Excuse me.
Hey! Three, four, five,
six, seven, eight!
-Have you cooked rice?
-Oh, no.
Hang on, I'm almost done!
Wait, I'm just…
I'm just wrapping this up. Wait a sec.
Don't bother. I'll do it.
Thank you, big sis!
-Wow, you never stop dancing.
-Ma!
Ma.
Uh, Ma… Do you have 250 pesos to spare?
Come on now, Jena.
I just got back from work,
and this is how you welcome me?
I just need it now, Ma…
Why are you telling me now?
You know my next paycheck's
still a long way off.
-Now…
-I've got this, Ma.
I just got my talent's fee.
Thank goodness!
By the way, your father has
used up all his medicine.
-Two hundred fifty. Here.
-Oh, thank you, big sis!
Mm-hmm.
Just make sure you study well.
Be like April. Always top of the class.
-Hey, I'm consistent too.
-Hmm?
-Consistently the class muse. Bam!
-Whoa.
My goodness.
Look at her.
She's destined to be a beauty queen.
And once April graduates,
I'll be living like royalty.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, happy birthday ♪
Happy birthday, dear.
Come on, blow out the candle.
But wait, you have to make a wish first.
Happy birthday, big sis!
Thank you, Papa.
I forgot it's your birthday.
My goodness. Why didn't you tell me?
Patricia, you should've said something.
I could've made noodles.
I've had so much on my mind
that I overlooked it.
-I'm sorry.
-It's all right, Ma.
You know I don't want any celebration.
-Dear…
-Yes?
-What is that?
-Oh…
Who hurt you? Tell me who did this!
Hey, hey! Pa, calm down!
We shot some action-heavy stuff,
but don't worry. It's nothing major.
So when do we get to see your scenes?
Forget it. You won't even
see my face there.
I was just the lead star's body double.
So you can't even watch your own work?
All I know is that someday…
you'll be the star.
Let's dig in! It looks delicious!
Psst, wait. Let your sister eat first.
Seems like you've got a drink ready, Pa.
Uh, well… It's your birthday.
So, let's celebrate.
-Hmm? You want to celebrate?
-Mm-hmm.
Well, my birthday wish
is for you to quit drinking.
-Come on.
-Nope, just stick to water.
-Right, Ma?
-Mm-hmm.
That's right.
Cut the pie later.
It's raw…
Call the chef.
-Walk faster.
-Yes, Ms. D?
This is raw.
It's just a little bit pink…
Of all the things I hate, it's excuses.
This is turkey. Poultry.
And isn't poultry
never served undercooked?
Do you want to give me salmonella?
Do you want me dead? You sit down.
-Ma'am?
-Sit down!
Taste it.
Delicious?
Mmm!
It's mine! I washed the dishes!
I scrubbed the bathroom!
Stop it, you two.
Give it to your sister,
she's exhausted from work.
Go on, have some more.
It's your day. Don't be shy.
It's okay. That's for you.
There, nice and even.
Everyone gets some. Here you go.
You're the best, big sis.
She's practically a saint.
You okay, Pa?
You're out of water. Wait, I'll get some.
Martin Dela Cruz,
come out and face us!
-That's right!
-Show your face!
-Get out here!
-Come outside!
Captain, what's the matter?
Your father took all of our money!
What?
-Pa.
-He said…
he'd help us get a livelihood package
from the government,
and we just needed
to pay a processing fee!
So we gave money to your father!
But then we learned it was all a lie!
-Exactly!
-Liar!
And you're probably
in cahoots with Carlota!
After all, she works at the town hall!
Hey, that's quite an accusation!
Martin is innocent!
Mr. Dimayuga is behind it all!
I don't know a thing!
He has your money!
Dimayuga has been arrested!
He said you still
haven't given him his cut!
Don't play dumb!
-That's right!
-Yes!
-Pa…
-Such a liar.
What are they talking about?
What did you do with their money?
Oh, please!
Don't pretend you know nothing!
I-I honestly didn't know!
Well, we know your family's deep in debt!
No wonder, you're all desperate!
You all deserve to be locked up!
-Right?
-Yes!
Come on, you don't need to do this.
He should rot in prison!
-Explain yourself, Martin!
-Hang on…
Wait a minute!
-Sir, please wait!
-That's him, sir!
Martin Dela Cruz,
come with us to the police station.
Wait, wait!
-Please, hang on!
-Wait a second!
Lock him up!
-Mister!
-Hold on!
-Don't hurt him!
Sir, take him!
Consider that your last meal
in this house.
Ma'am?
I don't have to prove myself
right all the time.
You're fired.
Hello?
Ms. D… Something went wrong
with the feeding program.
What went wrong?
There was food poisoning
at our feeding program
in Corpuz City.
They're pointing to Cala Soda
as the cause.
-What?
-There are already 125 victims
and still counting.
It's severe food poisoning, Ms. D.
Most of the victims
are children and the elderly.
Is it confirmed that our soda
is the source of poisoning?
Final lab results
are yet to be announced,
but the initial reports suggest
possible soda contamination.
Possible is not an answer.
From which plant was the product sourced?
Uh… Uh…
I will confirm that right now, Ms. D.
Shouldn't you have already
known that before I asked?
Give me an answer!
We've been in contact
with the hospital management
and the families of the victims.
We'll be responsible
for their hospital bills.
Call the legal department. Have them
prepare the compensation packages.
Noted, Ms. D.
Ms. D?
Burger City International is on the phone.
This is Diana Aragon.
Diana,
I'm gonna cut straight to the point.
We're very disappointed.
The initial launch… was unfortunate.
But manageable.
This situation is under control.
Investigation is underway.
Children being poisoned
is not a "situation."
Burger City International
cannot be affiliated
with that kind of controversy.
No, no, no.
Give me 24 hours. We can fix this.
We're fix-- We're on this.
The board has already made its decision.
We're terminating our partnership,
effective immediately.
I'm sorry, Diana.
No, no, no, but--
-Call them again.
-Yes, ma'am.
Georgia is calling them right now.
Auntie.
Auntie, they're not answering anymore.
No response either, Ms. D.
Can anyone tell me what caused this?
Does anybody here know
what caused this thing?
This whole thing? No one?
Nothing?
Do you even know
what's at stake in this deal?
Now I'm losing it
because you can't give me an answer!
Did I hire freaking imbeciles?
How did this happen?
I cannot--
I will not lose this partnership deal!
I need to get to the bottom of this!
Right now! I need answers!
Give me answers!
-Ms. D…
-Ms. D?
-Ms. D!
-Diana! Diana!
-Auntie!
-Call an ambulance!
-Get an ambulance!
Hurry! Ms. D? Ms. D?
Diana…
Patient still has no pulse.
-Showing signs of V-tach.
-Continue CPR.
-Charge the defibrillator…
-No pulse.
to 200 joules, biphasic.
-Three. Everybody clear?
-Clear!
ELECTRICITY ₱1,650
WATER ₱700
RENT ₱3,000
SAVINGS FOR TUITION ₱2,000
Don't tell me
you'll spend that too.
You've been saving that for months.
For rent.
And weren't you setting aside
money for tuition
because you want to study again?
I'll just save up again.
What matters is that
we post bail for Papa.
But big sis… Will that be enough?
I'm not really sure.
-I'll pawn this too.
-And then what?
Once it's pawned, will that cover it?
Isn't there a popular lending app?
Help me download it.
But they've got a high interest rate.
We can worry about that later.
I hate this life!
Why did we have to be born poor?
I wish we were nepo babies,
swimming in money.
Or the missing heirs
with a grandfather searching for us
to give us everything! That kind of life!
That only happens in the movies, Jena.
Where someone has to die
before the heiress inherits.
Where did I even see that?
On Facegram, right?
-Was it there?
-Let me help.
Let's check. Wait.
Hang on, what's this?
We are currently at Central Crest Hospital
and Medical Center, where the CEO
of La Familia Bottling Company
is reportedly confined.
Based on initial reports,
Diana Aragon,
known as the "Chairmom" of La Familia,
suffered a heart attack
after the issue of food poisoning
in one of their feeding programs erupted.
Cala Soda is being pointed to
as the cause of the poisoning.
We are still waiting for a statement
from her brother, Teodoro Aragon.
Aside from him, Ms. Aragon
has no other immediate family.
But according to the information
we gathered,
Ms. Aragon has a daughter.
Wow. A missing daughter?
Lucky her! She's an instant heiress!
In the midst
of the uncertain situation,
the question on everyone's minds is:
where is the sole heiress of La Familia?
Mama!
Ma'am…
Excuse me. Who are you?
Sir, I'm the real daughter
of Diana Aragon!
Where is my mother?
-Where--
-No, that's not true!
I'm the real daughter of Diana Aragon!
-Excuse--
-Hang on! Don't believe them!
I'm her real daughter!
Do they look rich at all?
Wait a minute--
-Argh! Nurse, my stomach hurts!
-What's wrong, ma'am?
Let me wheel you in.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Excuse me! Everyone, listen up!
Have some respect for Ms. D.
Please.
You all need to go right now, okay?
-Guards, please.
-Yes, sir.
Hey, Daryl!
Dr. Reyes has been looking for you.
I have a patient.
Uh, no, you can leave me now.
-Are you sure you'll be okay?
-Yes. Thank you.
-All right, then.
-Brace yourself.
-Just leave, ma'am.
-This way, please.
Guards, please secure the perimeter.
-Yes, sir.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Unbelievable!
Didn't we already tell you press people?
-No coverage for now.
-Just one question, sir.
We're not ready to make
a statement at this time.
Okay?
Please, get out of here.
Jena.
Pa!
Pa, you're back!
-Pa!
-Oh, sweetie.
How was it? Are you okay?
Wasn't the bed uncomfortable?
Wasn't it hot there, Pa?
It was a little hot, but I'm fine.
-I'm just worried about your feet…
-Pa…
Oh, they missed you so much.
-I'll make you a cup of coffee.
-Thanks.
How'd your night go?
We're out of coffee.
Did you ask your sister to buy some?
Oh, my!
Ma, I reminded her.
But she might've forgotten
while fixing Papa's mess.
Look, Pa… I'm glad she found a way
to cover your bail.
Hold on.
Where did she get the money?
She used her savings, and borrowed money.
She even pawned her necklace.
I'll just pay her back.
Where's your sister, anyway?
I have no idea, Ma.
She said she'd be here.
I was the only one without a mom.
Mama probably has important work
at the office, dear.
More important than me?
At least Papa is here.
Come on, Papa.
It's Mother's Day. You're not a mother.
Hey, I have an idea.
Let's go get ice cream.
Even though
Mama says sweets are bad for me?
We'll keep it our little secret.
Okay?
You need this.
Thank you.
Is it obvious my head hurts?
I've memorized
every wrinkle on your forehead.
You don't need to keep doing this.
You're already the company's bookkeeper.
Does that mean I should stop
being friends with you?
Of course not.
I wonder how I would manage without you.
Oh, could you take this off?
-Help me, please.
-Why?
Doesn't it go better with your dress?
Are you sure?
What, is this a loan or a gift?
It's a gift, obviously.
Never a loan.
Excuse me. Patricia.
What are you doing?
I want to blow out the candle now.
My gosh! Will you stop it? Please!
You never use just your hands
when you eat, okay?
You have to keep yourself neat
and clean and presentable.
Look at Enzo and Georgia over there.
They're well-behaved.
They actually listen
to what their parents say.
I just don't understand why
you're so stubborn, dear.
What's the use of being an Aragon
if Papa can't trust me
to lead the company?
-Am I right?
-Absolutely.
But you know what? One day…
I want to move away from the shadows
and build my own company.
-That's the spirit.
-I know, right?
Where's the dress I bought for you?
Why are you wearing this?
It was itchy.
Plus, it's my birthday.
Exactly, dear. It's your birthday.
You should've worn it.
It's a pretty dress.
You're very pretty. What a waste!
And now look at you.
You stained your outfit.
That's fine.
Martin, look at what she did to the cake.
She poked it.
She poked it and had a taste.
She stained her outfit.
She destroyed the cake.
Now it's all ruined.
Oh, relax.
This is why your daughter never learns.
Patricia is just a kid.
Let her have fun.
It's her birthday today.
Sure, but when will she learn?
When she's all grown up?
-Come on now.
-Hey… My wife's way too serious.
-Oh, please.
-Come on.
I'll look after Patricia.
I'll take care of her.
Let me.
Martin, stay with Diana.
She's been stressed out.
Fine, team up against me again.
Oh, you two.
-Martin!
-Hmm?
What are you doing?
Papa doesn't want you smoking! Put it out!
Fine, fine. I won't smoke.
How much did you drink?
Fix yourself, hmm?
-Oh, I need to…
-Hey.
-What?
-You know the drill.
-Oh, my gosh, Martin.
-Let's dance.
-It's embarrassing.
-Come here.
-You've too much-- See?
-Hold on.
-Argh.
See? How much did you drink?
-Let's enjoy!
-How much did you drink?
-Come on, turn. Turn.
- Stop it!
-Yes! Yes!
-I think you're drunk.
Sorry, sir.
-Excuse me.
-Oh, sure, sure.
I'm sorry. Don't mind it.
Nothing to worry about.
It's just wine glass.
We have a lot of it.
And we have more drinks,
so let's keep the party going.
I think you got this all wrong.
This isn't a family day event.
This event was created for business.
Maybe you forgot that it's also
your granddaughter's birthday today.
Don't you have any other necklace
that isn't tacky?
Come on, dear.
Diana, let's go.
Diana.
Attorney Ignacio is here
and we need to talk to him.
This is important.
Follow me. Now.
The company started
as an sugar mill.
Until we ventured into drinks.
Since then, we have been loved
by every Filipino
across many generations.
Tonight is not just about looking back.
Tonight is also about looking forward.
Because a family business
isn't just passed down
to the next generation.
It should be protected
and preserved.
Long live La Familia!
Hey, Martin.
Martin, stop it. It's embarrassing.
Get it together.
And now,
for the success
of our newest product.
The Cala Soda.
A product years in development.
And only reminds us
that legacy can't be inherited.
It is something one must work hard for.
Martin!
-Papa!
-Martin, please.
I'm so sorry.
-I'm okay.
-M-Martin…
Cheers, Lucio!
To other people's hard work
that's been taken advantage of
by a greedy family!
The shameless family, the Aragons!
See this?
Do you see this?
This Cala Soda? It's mine!
It came from me!
I made the recipe!
But after all the hard work I put into it,
he promoted his daughter instead!
And when I complained,
they had the guts to fire me!
Guards, get this woman out!
I'm telling the truth!
-You are thieves!
-Hurry up!
-It's okay, it's okay.
-You're all thieves!
Liars!
Happy birthday to me
♪ Happy birthday to me ♪
Happy birthday, Patricia!
Damn it. You're not being careful.
Hurry up and fix it.
Put in the recycle bin.
Hurry and get it all off so I can go.
Oh, my cake!
Ah!
Help!
-Mama!
-Dear!
Let's get out of here, dear!
-Carry her there!
-Let's go!
Mommy! Mommy! Mommy!
-Oh, my god.
-Mommy! Mommy!
Diana! Diana!
-Diana, are you okay?
-Carlota!
Where's Papa?
Does he know what's going on here?
I haven't seen him since the party.
-But I'll ask around.
-Please do!
Find out if he already knows,
then tell me.
Okay, okay.
You all right?
Just stay here, okay?
I'll go inside to help.
-Okay.
-Look after Patricia.
Yes, I got her.
What's this?
Why do you have this?
-Huh?
-It's for the candle on my cake.
Where did you light the candle?
Inside the factory?
Did you light it inside the factory?
Patricia, tell me! What did you do?
Mama, I didn't do it!
It hurts!
Oh, god.
Oh, good god!
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god!
Faster, please!
Hurry! Help him!
-Papa! P-Papa!
-Diana.
Let the rescuers do their jobs.
Let me go! Papa!
Papa!
Diana.
-Papa!
-Mama!
Let me go! Papa!
-Papa!
-Let them treat him!
I'll get some rest.
Mama…
Hello.
Okay, I'll be there in 30 minutes.
Argh! Do it! Argh!
Argh!
You'll pay for your crimes!
You can't get away from the law!
So this is why you keep failing.
All you do is watch TV.
I thought you were struggling,
that's why I hired a tutor for you.
You answered letter D
for all of the items in your exam.
What really is the problem?
Are you being bullied in school? Tell me.
Is there something wrong
with your teacher?
Do they scold you?
Or do you just refuse to learn?
-Answer me.
-None of the above.
Patricia, I've got a lot
going on right now.
Don't make it any worse, dear!
Did you hear that? "None of the above?"
You have a family
to take care of!
All you do is work
for that freaking company!
"Freaking company?"
The company that supports you-- Us?
I'm not the only one benefiting from it!
All of us do!
Fine, you're better than me!
You are the boss.
But I'm not just your employee,
Diana, I'm your husband!
Even after what you did to me,
you're still my husband.
Have you forgotten, Martin,
how I defended you to Papa?
And how hard I fought for this family?
We wouldn't have any problems
if you weren't a suck-up to your dad!
You should've been
a good wife to me,
and a present mother to your child!
You have a lot more shortcomings
than I do!
Papa was right.
I made a mistake marrying you.
You know what, Martin?
We've been through this over and over.
You've always blamed the company,
and you direct your anger to the company.
I'm tired of fighting about this.
Let's separate.
All right! All right, let's separate!
I'm getting tired of being your husband!
Do you really think
you're the only one suffering
in this relationship?
Well…
then leave.
Leave!
Mama!
Don't ask Papa to leave!
P-Patricia, were you there the whole time?
Dear…
Why are you asking Papa to leave?
Your mama doesn't want me anymore
-because I'm poor.
-Martin!
Am I the only one at fault here?
Now you're throwing me out, and you think
it's a mistake getting married
just because you got pregnant.
You think having Patricia
is a mistake too, is that it?
Martin, don't you dare!
Patricia, dear, please stay outside.
Papa and I need to talk, okay?
You're always mad at Papa!
-You don't love us!
-What?
Please don't go, Papa! I'll come with you!
-Don't leave me with her!
-P-Patricia!
Patricia…
do you really think I'll let that happen?
I'm your mama.
If I stay here, will I be with you?
You're always away!
You don't understand.
You don't understand!
You're blaming me
for what happened to Grandpa!
What did you say?
It's true!
Ever since Grandpa died,
you've always been mad at me!
You don't love me anymore!
You wish I were dead instead of him!
Patricia, don't say that!
Martin, don't. Martin, no. No, Martin!
Martin, give me my daughter!
Martin!
Because your child
is over seven years old,
we need to listen to what she has to say
and give value
to her choice or preference.
Patricia,
do you want to be
with your mama or your papa?
I want to be with Papa.
Nanny Cora, is Diana around?
I need to talk to her.
Carlota, I'm so sorry. She's not here.
Don't lie! I know she's here--
She's right there! Diana!
Diana!
Diana, Martin got into an accident!
We need your help!
Ma'am, I'm sorry,
I have to ask you to leave.
Diana!
Diana, please! Help Martin!
-Ma'am, I'm sorry.
-Carlota, just leave.
Ma, let's just go!
Let's just go! They don't want us here!
-They don't want us here!
-Please leave.
-Diana!
-Let's go, Ma!
-Please, Carlota!
-Let's go!
Diana, I'm begging you!
Ma, let's go! I'll find a way!
I got this! Let's go!
Code blue! Code blue!
Ms. D?
Am I not supposed to be here?
I just don't want Diana to be agitated.
What if she wakes up
and sees you first thing?
What do you need? Money?
-Someone came to visit you.
-The Grim Reaper?
-It's Patricia.
-Where is she?
Can we stay here?
We've got nowhere else to go.
Patricia is still your daughter.
You think she still sees me as her mom?
You have to tell them the truth.
And that should fix everything?
People think they know your whole story.
You're all alone now
because no one can stand you!
-Please stop.
-Enough!